Today, i wil show you an application that's built on Win32API with C/C++.
The program name is PaymentAnalyzer

Firstly, my name is Nghĩa - 1412344

In this app, im using ListView, Listbox, GDI+, OOP and some magic :D

Let's start.

this is the app interface (UI)

in the first dropbox, u can choose the one of those payment-type. then u fill in the next box the content, what you have bought. And the money you paid. 
Finally, u click "Thêm" Button.